Contact

akshaybankar1004@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/akshay-bankar-68784b259 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

TensorFlow

Natural Language Processing (NLP) Business Analytics

Akshay Bankar

Data Scientist || Data Analytics || Machine Learning || Python || MySQL || Business Analyst

Pune, Maharashtra, India

Summary

Data scientist with 3+ years of experience having strong verbal and written communication skills and knowledge of building Machine Learning Algorithm and Exploratory Data Analysis and provide decision making insights alongside art of story telling.

Experience

Tiger Analytics Senior Analyst - Data Science March 2024 - Present (1 year 1 month) Hyderabad, Telangana, India

Etraveli Group CS Insights Analyst February 2023 - September 2023 (8 months) Mumbai, Maharashtra, India

Tenet Technology
Data Scientist
February 2021 - January 2023 (2 years)

Education

Savitribai Phule Pune University

Masters in Engineering · (October 2015 - October 2017)

Shivaji University, Kolhapur Bachelor of Engineering - BE · (July 2011 - July 2015)